const questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "Life is not a theme park, and if it is, the theme is death.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "„There is going to be a revolution.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question:
      "It is illusory to expect that one can actually change things by extending democracy.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "Why vote? We know it i's not going to make any difference.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question:
      "We are too narcissistic to risk any kind of accidental trip or fall. Even into love!",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question:
      "Of all the consumer products, chewing gum is perhaps the most ridiculous: it literally has no nourishment – you just chew it to give yourself something to do with your stupid idiot western mouth.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question: "„99% of people are boring idiots.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question:
      "Nowadays, you can do anything that you want – anal, oral, fisting – but you need to be wearing gloves, condoms, protection.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question:
      "The threat today is not passivity but pseudo-activity, the urge to ‘be active’, to ‘participate’, to mask the Nothingness of what goes on.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question:
      "You must not feel persecuted and examined. Liberate yourself from that idea that people are watching you.",
    answers: ["Brand", "Žižek"],
    correct: 0
  }
];

export default questions;
